Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Files Regarding Wages (1949-1964) (Box 17)
  - Wages - International Union: President's Emergency Board, Employee's Exhibit: Car retarder operations, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Wages- International Union: President's Emergency Board, Employee's Exhibit: Work week reduction, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Wages - International Union: President's Emergency Board, Employee's Exhibit: Daily earning minimum, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Wages - International Union: President's Emergency Board, Employee's Exhibit: Proposition, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Wages - International Union: President's Emergency Board, Employee's Exhibit. Wage differentials, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America report on 40 hour work week, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Manuscript, correspondence. 1950, 1955
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America Request management for wage increase and 5-day work week, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Wages - International Union. Employee's Exhibit - Switchmen's Union of North America. Workweek reduction Premium pay for overtime, etc., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America Wages and rules agreement, rates of pay, 1950-1959 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America, wages, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, manuscripts, pamphlets
  - Wages - International Union: Dispute between Eastern Western, Southeastern Carriers Conference Committee and SUNA, BLE, and BLF and E. Supplement 3, 1956., 1953-1956 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    A-B. Switchmen's Union of North America, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen. Manuscript. 1953, 1956.
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America, stand by agreements with various railroads, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    A-1 - E-1. Correspondence, manuscript.
  - Wages - International Union: Wage Scrapbook from SUNA (Box 17, Folder 25)
    Miscellaneous pamphlets, clippings, etc. No date.
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America wage file, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    A-B. Correspondence.
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America form letters regarding wage movement, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America wage movement, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America referendum on wage issue, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Wages - International Union: Wage - court case, United States Court of Appeals, Docket Number 26739. Chicago, Rhode Island and Pacific Railway Company versus SUNA, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    Switchmen's Union of North America. Correspondence.
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America correspondence regarding wage settlement, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Wages - International Union: Complaints from locals regarding wage proposal, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America wage movement of 1959, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    A-1 - C-1. Correspondence
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America agreement Western Carriers Mediation document on wages propaganda pamphlet, 1962- 1964 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    Manuscript. 1962, 1964.
- Files Regarding Wages (1964-1967), Vacations (1940-1966), and Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America. All correspondence on Section 6 Wage Notice to all Railroads, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    A-G. Correspondence
  - Wages - International Union. Switchmen's Union of North America Wage Rules, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America wage notice, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, manuscript
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    correspondence
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America proposal of wage committees, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America National Wage Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America National Wage Issue, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Wages - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America wage chronology - 1936-1937, pamphlet, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Vacations - International Union: 5 brotherhoods - Joint concerted movement, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Vacations - International Union: Cashen - Testimony on vacations, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Vacations - International Union: Correspondence by BLF and E, ORC, and SUNA, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors, and Switchmen's Union of North America. Correspondence.
  - Vacations - International Union: Operating Employees' vacation agreements and decisions of committees established by section 10, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Vacations - International Union: Consolidated uniform Agreement, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    A-B. Manuscript. July 1945
  - Vacations - International Union: Correspondence regarding meeting between carriers and brotherhoods on vacation, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, and Switchmen's Union of North America. Correspondence. January-February 1945
  - Vacations - International Union: Correspondence, vacation agreement of 5 operating brotherhoods, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Manuscript, correspondence. March-June 1945
  - Vacations - International Union: Vacation disputes, 1945-1955 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Vacations - International Union: Agreement, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Switchmen's Union of North America agreement. Correspondence.
  - Vacations - International Union: Agreement, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Eastern, Western, South Eastern Carriers and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, and Switchmen's Union of North America. April 29, 1949. Manus
  - Vacations - International Union: Vacation agreements and decisions, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    A-1 - E-1. Order of Railway Conductors, Switchmen's Union of North America, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen. Correspondence, manuscript.
  - Vacations - International Union: Correspondence regarding BLE, BLF and E, SUNA, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Switchmen's Union of North America. Correspondence.
  - Vacations - International Union: Meeting - correspondence on agreement, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: MinutesMeetingSpecial conference of the Railways and Switchmen's Union of North America Numbers 1-2, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Correspondence regarding Appointment to Railroad Labor Board, 1920-1922 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - - International Union: Correspondence regarding appointment on Labor Board, 1920-1923 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America and Railroad Yardmasters of North America, 1924-1952 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Switchmen's Union of North America regarding action regarding picket lines, 1937- 1950 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Correspondence regarding Ladies Auxiliary Switchmen's Union of North America Proceedings 1941, 1938-1958 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    Correspondence, pamphlet
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Correspondence regarding Railroads and World War II, 1940-1943 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    A-3 - B-3. Correspondence.
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Cases not settled by individual Committees, 1940-1942 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Switchmen's Union of North America versus ACY (?). Correspondence.
  - Miscellaneous 0 International Union: Correspondence between Switchmen's Union of North America and Yardmasters of America, 1941-1952 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    A-4 - B-4. Correspondence
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Office Circular, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Switchmen's Union of North America. Correspondence.
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: 5 brotherhoods correspondence on Association on Colored Railway Trainmen and Locomotive Firemen, Incorporated, 1943- 1946 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1946.
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Correspondence regarding Switchmen's Union of North America "Journal", 1948 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, statement
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Papers Report and Investigate an unadjusted dispute Denver and Rio Grande Western BLE, BLF and E, ORC, SUNA, BRT, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    A-5 - B-5. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors, Switchmen's Union of North America, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Correspondence, manuscript, etcetera.
- Miscellaneous Files; Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Akron, Canton and Youngstown-Buffalo Creek Railway) (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America organizing on various railroads, 1950-1957 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Correspondence on piggy backing, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Switchmen's Union of North America Legal File - Regional Counsels; relates to legal matter in California, 1955-1959 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    A-1 - E-1. Correspondence, manuscripts.
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Right to work correspondence. Manuscript on Defense of Min. (?) Yard Crews New York State, 1958-1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Newsletter BLE, BLF and E, ORC and B, BRT, SUNA, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    A-2 - B-2. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Switchmen's Union of North America. Pamphlets.
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: SUNA versus BRT, ORC and B, SUNA Division 584 of BRT, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Switchmen's Union of North America versus Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, Switchmen's Union of North America Division 584 of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Manuscript.
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: General Grievance Fund, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous - International Union: Special Board Adjustments Numbers 390, 785, 1961-1966 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Akron, Canton and Youngstown - Agreement, Correspondence, 1937-1946 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    A-C. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Akron, Canton, and Youngstown - W.F. Grimm, H.G. Watkins (General Superintendent of Akron, Canton, and Youngstown Railroad), and T. Cashen (Pres. Of SUNA), 1939-1940 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    T. Cashen: President of Switchmen's Union of North America. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Akron, Canton, and Youngstown - Memorandum of Understanding, related correspondence, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Akron, Canton and Youngstown - Work sheets, seniority list (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Correspondence. No date.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railroad Grievance Case - W.E. Riddle and H.G. Watkins; National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Akron, Canton and Youngstown - Dispute Lodge 295 and Akron, Canton and Youngstown (Timeslips and Piloting), 1941 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Akron, Canton, and Youngstown Railroad - J.J. Savage and T. Cashen (seniority, armed forces, dismissal of W.L. Casey), 1942 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Alabama and Vicksburg Railway Company - Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railway Company. John Dundas, T. Cashen., 1925- 1926 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, agreement.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Parties to dispute - SUNA and Alameda Belt Line Case Number SUNA-4-W - Alameda Belt Line vs. SUNA Case Number ABL-14, 1943- 1966 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    SUNA: Switchmen's Union of North America. Memorandum agreement, correspondence. 1943, 1966.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Alameda Belt Line (wages), 1966 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Alton and Southern Railway Company (agreement with Switchmen's Union of North America - pay, rules, etcetera), 1935 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Dispute - Alton and Southern Railway Manufacturers with SUNA to act as arbitrator. T.C. \, D.B. Robertson, 1939-1940 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    SUNA: Switchmen's Union of North America. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Letter General Grievance Committee Atchison Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. J. Larkin, H.S. Dean, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Atlas Powder company - Correspondence and agreement on wages and working rules, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Baltimore and Ohio - Unclassified demands, letter, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Cases of W.F. Ball, on Baltimore and Ohio, 1954; Membership report of Switchmen's Union on Baltimore and Ohio (Box 19, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, membership report
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union shop agreement, Baltimore and Ohio Employee, E. Donnelly and Switchmen's Union of North America, 1955-1957 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Baltimore and Ohio correspondence with G. Blanchard of Switchmen's Union of North America, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    Correspondence - general - Baltimore and Ohio - Switchmen's Union of North America.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Baltimore and Ohio and Switchmen's Union of North America cases (claims) settled, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Baltimore and Ohio and Switchmen's Union of North America claims settled, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    A-D. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Baltimore and Ohio and Switchmen's Union of North America claims settled, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Baltimore, Ohio, Chicago T. Company, 1917-1928 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    A-1 - B-1. Agreement, Correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: Belt Railway Company of Chicago - Agreement, wages and working rules, etcetera, 1917-1964 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    Correspondence. 1917, 1963, 1964
  - Agreement and Strike File: Bessemer and Lake Erie Railway Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    Memorandum, agreement, correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: Switchmen's Union of North America and Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal. T.C. Cashen, E. Teichert., 1922-1924 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, Docket Case 2034 - Wages
  - Agreement and Strike File: Buffalo Creek Railway, 1943-1958 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Buffalo Creek Railway Claims, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Buffalo Creek Railway - Barone Case, 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Coupling Air Hose Arbitration - Switchmen's Union of North America and Buffalo Creek Railway, 1950-1955 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Buffalo Creek Railway - Claims, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Buffalo Creek Railway - Agreement, correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    Correspondence. 1954, 1960.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Buffalo Creek Railway - wages, health and welfare, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    Correspondence. 1964, 1966
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Canadian Pacific Railway-Chicago Great Western) (Box 20)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Canadian Pacific Railway - Appropriate bargaining unit for Canadian Pacific Railway, 1921-1951 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Correspondence. 1921, 1951
  - Agreement and Strike File: Camas Prairie - Health and welfare wage notice, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Correspondence. 1964, 1966.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Central of Georgia -, 1949-1967 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    A-1 - B-1. Agreements (1961, 1965, 1949); General Adjustment Committee 1962-1965, 1967; Interstate Commerce Commission Docket 21400 V-SUNA-2-SE, SUNA-3-SE, SUNA 15-W, SUNA 16-W. Correspondence, agreements, decisions.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Central of Georgia - Memorandum of agreement (pay regulations, proposed rules), 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, schedule of pay and regulations, proposal of rules
  - Agreement and Strike File: Central of Georgia - General Correspondence, 1956-1959 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Central of Georgia - Wage notice, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Central New England Railway - Prepare for strike, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Central Railroad of New Jersey - Question of representation, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: SUNA and Central Railroad of New Jersey - Electing SUNA to represent workers, resume of cases, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    SUNA: Switchmen's Union of North America. Legal document.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Central of New Jersey - Question of representation, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chesapeake and Ohio - Wages and working conditions (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chesapeake and Ohio - organizing, 1933-1947 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Correspondence. 1933, 1947
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago, Burlington, Quincy Railway - Stipulation and Agreement, Finance Dockets 16047, 16456, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western Railway - miscellaneous, 1902-1918 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Includes: Rules, wages 1902, 1907, 1910, 1917, minutes of General Committee, arbitration awards and correspondence, miscellaneous.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence, agreement on pay rates 1919, three separate agreements, 1919-1920 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Manuscript. January-May 1921
  - Agreement and Strike file: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Manuscript. June-December 1921
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Docket 4227, Wheeler Case, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Manuscript. January 1924
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence on working conditions; Case of Meindl on wages, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    Manuscript. February 1924
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Agreements (Case of C.J. Leavitt and Scanlon Correspondence), 1924 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Manuscript. March- June 1924
  - Agreement and Strike file: Chicago Great Western - Case of Mend, Strike of dining car 1924 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Manuscript. July-December 1924
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Decision 3969, Wheeler, Docket 4727; Decision 3968, Meindl, Docket 4726, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - General Correspondence, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - General Correspondence, 1927-1929 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Case of Ned Brink before General Adjustment Committee, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Merger with St. Paul Bridge and Terminal Company, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Brief, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    Manuscript. October 31-November 10, 1936
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - General Committee meeting question strike brief on United States District Court 58970, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence Docket 2156, memorandum on agreement, January 1936 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Dispute refusal of carrier to put in effect National Railroad Adjustment Board awards, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    A- B. Manuscript.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Case: Fred Doty, claims, correspondence, General Adjustment Commission, circulars, agreement, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    A-1 - F-1. Manuscript.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Dispute and arbitration case 58970, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Chicago Great Western - Memorandum and correspondence on case 58970, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    Manuscript. January 1937
  - Agreement and Strike file: Chicago Great Western - miscellaneous, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    Includes: Correspondence, minutes of joint meetings of 5 brotherhoods, Emergency Board, Railway Labor Act. Manuscript. February 1937.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence, brief, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    Manuscript. February 1937
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Chicago Great Western-Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific) (Box 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Report of Emergency Board: BLF and E, BLE, BRT, ORC, and SUNA vs. Chicago Great Western, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Order of Railway Conductors, and Switchmen's Union of North America. Manuscript. March 1937.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence and awards, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Manuscript. March-April 1937
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Manuscript. April-July 1937
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Seniority roster, yard polls, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Manuscript. August 1937
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - Yard polls, correspondence, agreement 1937 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Manuscript. September-November 1937.
  - Agreement and Strike file: Chicago Great Western - Regarding abolishment of $2.00 assessment, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - General, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Manuscript. February-April 1939
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western: General, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Manuscript. May-June 1939
  - Agreement and Strike File: Chicago Great Western - General, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Manuscript. June-July 1939